<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><?xml-stylesheet type="text/xml" href="http://utkarshbansal.me//feed.xslt.xml"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.3.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://utkarshbansal.me//feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://utkarshbansal.me//" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2017-01-29T11:51:30+05:30</updated><id>http://utkarshbansal.me///</id><title type="html">Utkarsh Bansal</title><author><name>Utkarsh Bansal</name><email>contact@utkarshbansal.me</email></author><entry><title type="html">Hello World</title><link href="http://utkarshbansal.me//blog/Hello-World/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Hello World" /><published>2017-01-26T00:00:00+05:30</published><updated>2017-01-26T00:00:00+05:30</updated><id>http://utkarshbansal.me//blog/Hello%20World</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://utkarshbansal.me//blog/Hello-World/">&lt;p&gt;So the year is 2017 and AI has already taken over the world… 
It controlls the evolution of the human species and chooses the leader of the free world among others. No joke, I’m
serious, think about it. An AI that builds our Tinder feed is basically deciding who we have our kids with and hence 
ultimately controlling the evolution of the human species. Another AI - Google, controlls what information we see by
controlling our search results and hence controlls our opinions and knowledge about politics hence choosing the leader
of the free world - POTUS. And this is just the tip of the iceberg. Today in 2017, I can’t evening begin to list the 
things that an AI controlls for me - it’s just everwhere.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay so I wandered off there, coming back to myself - Hi there! I am Utkarsh Bansal and I’m currently pursuing my
bachelor’s degree in Computer Science and Technology. This, here is my first blog post. I never thought that I’ll setup 
a blog but here I am with Jekyll. &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;Jekyll&lt;/code&gt; is, in my opion quite cool. It got me blogging in no time and still gves me 
complete controll over the blog. Best of all - its hosted on &lt;em&gt;Github Pages&lt;/em&gt; and doesn’t need a database, so I don’t 
have to remember another password and I don’t need to manage another server.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thats all for now, I’ll keep wiritng every now and then.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Utkarsh Bansal</name><email>contact@utkarshbansal.me</email></author><summary type="html">So the year is 2017 and AI has already taken over the world... It controlls the evolution of the human species and chooses the leader of the free world, among other things.</summary></entry></feed>
